<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>4M Mehni's Misc Modifications (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.4MMehnisMiscModifications</packageId>
  <author>Mehni, XeoNovaDan, simplyWiri, Miyuri (ZXfkSIE), Kaedys</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/4MMehnisMiscModifications</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Mehnis mod https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2228765246

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr][td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td] [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/4MMehnisMiscModifications][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/h5VwTNL.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Adds various settings to customise your RimWorld experience.

[h1]FEATURES[/h1]
- Bugfixes for vanilla issues
The game gives up on sending you manhunter packs once you reach a certain size. No more!

- Extend the time for pawns to undraft themselves
Stay where I put you!
Ever had colonists auto undraft themselves while positioning them? Not anymore.

- Change the threshold at which pawns retreat
Raiders flee at 50% by default. That's boring. Let's randomise the flee threshold.
Want a bigger challenge? Turn off fleeing entirely. Want a laid back game? Set it lower!
Want unpredictability? There's a slider for however much randomness you can suffer.
PS: doesn't work with those kamikaze groups which will fight until last person standing.

- Get an alert when the Nutrient Paste Dispenser can't be used
Pawns won't eat Nutrient Paste for some reason? Odds are there's a chunk blocking access to the interaction spot. 4M gives you a warning if this is the case.

[b]Information improvements[/b]
- Show what pawns are in a relationship when assigning beds
- Show more info on plant yield (Thanks XeoNovaDan!)
- Show DPS info for all (modded) weapons (Thanks XeoNovanDan!)
- Disable messages for dying animals - who cares about Chicken #357 dying?
- Confirmation dialog before starting if currently viewed colonist isn't selected for embark
- [strike]Better raider visibility. No more ninja mechanoids! All hostiles will have their label draw in red, whether they're a raider, mechanoid or hostile animal.[/strike] (Removed in 1.4, please use [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2904510148]Atomic Patches - Hostile Labels[/url] instead)
- Chased refugees will give a full headcount of their raid.
- Add item information buttons at item filter.

[b]Various (AI) tweaks and settings[/b]
- Never roll pacifists again.
- [strike]Set a custom filth rate for humans.[/strike] (Removed in 1.3)
- Don't interact with animals just before their naptime.
- Animals marked for taming are less tasty to your guard-trained predators. ("Bad bear! I said tame the turtle, not eat it!")
- Increase the size of Herd Migrations. Bring on the herd!

[b]Mods for modders[/b]
- Remove the 6 second cooldown on workshop submissions
- Devmode spawn tweaks. Pick the stuff and quality for the item you wish to spawn.
- [strike]Remove the 999 messages limit. Because sometimes you want to get spammed[/strike]. (Removed in 1.3)

Most things in the mod are optional which can be configured or turned off.

[h1]CREDITS[/h1]
Programmed by Mehni, XeoNovaDan, simplyWiri, Miyuri and Kaedys.
Chinese translation by HawnHan and Miyuri.
Japanese translation by Miyuri.
Preview image by Dianne. [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/diannetea/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Check out her stuff here![/url]
Many thanks to all kind mod developers at the official [url=https://discord.com/invite/K4wQe57]Discord server[/url]!

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list] 

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/3352204451][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/4MMehnisMiscModifications?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url] | tags:  tweaks,  customization</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.6.0</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>